<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Movie Shelf</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="cook_up_with_storm"><b>(Food, Comedy, Romance)</b></string>

    <string name="movies_details_description">Young Greg Heffley is looking forward to a long summer of just hanging out, but his mother throws a monkey wrench into his plans when she forces the entire family to take a road trip for a relative birthday celebration.
    Young Greg Heffley is looking forward to a long summer of just hanging out, but his mother throws a monkey wrench into his plans when she forces the entire family to take a road trip for a relative birthday.</string>
    <string name="movies_review"><u>Reviews</u></string>
    <string name="movies_fan_review"><i>John Chard wrote :</i></string>
    <string name="movies_details_full_preview">Every single sight gag in “Diary of a Wimpy Kid: The Long Haul” telegraphs its punchline for what seems like an eternity. Anyone, young or old, who sees the movie — the fourth in a series of films based on Jeff Kinney’s books — can probably predict how each setup will pay off. It’s about as subtle as an anvil landing on your foot.
        Whether the joke involves exploding baked goods, pigeon poop raining through a sunroof or teen antihero Greg Heffley (Jason Drucker) searching for his baby brother in a ball pit and coming up with a dirty diaper instead — an image that goes viral — the comic mayhem plays out in a slow, wait-for-it rhythm. When Greg’s trickster of a big brother Rodrick (Charlie Wright) eats a stick of fried butter at a country fair, then goes on a gravity-defying ride, you know exactly what’s going to happen. Every situation heralds a shameless ba-dum-BUM payoff.
        Still, as a low comedy about crazed middle-American family life, “The Long Haul” pretty much delivers on its promise, diapers and all. At least the ratio of giggles to groans runs about 50/50.The inspiration for the film is the ninth book in Kinney’s “Wimpy Kid” series about a small-for-his-age middle-schooler who longs to be cool and popular — and fails miserably. While “The Long Haul” has a totally new cast from the earlier movies — whose child actors are college-age now — director David Bowers helmed the last two releases
        (2011’s “Rodrick Rules” and 2012’s “Dog Days”) and co-wrote the latest screenplay with author Kinney.

        "\n""\n"Thus, the tone strongly echoes the earlier films, and the animated line drawings based on Kinney’s illustrations still wittily punctuate the action. Butthe level of gross-out humor feels amped up, and the absence of Greg’s school friends on this road trip leaves a comedic void.
        On top of all that utter humiliation, Greg completely oblivious parents announce that the whole family is going to pack into the family van again and take a four-day road trip to Granny Meemaw 90th birthday celebration. Talk about the start of a memorable summer.
        If Greg can finagle his way into a Mac Digby video, not only will it eclipse all this Diaper Hand business, why, it will redeem the whole summer. … No, it will make his whole life.

         "\n""\n"Thus, the tone strongly echoes the earlier films, and the animated line drawings based on Kinney’s illustrations still wittily punctuate the action. Butthe level of gross-out humor feels amped up, and the absence of Greg’s school friends on this road trip leaves a comedic void.
        On top of all that utter humiliation, Greg completely oblivious parents announce that the whole family is going to pack into the family van again and take a four-day road trip to Granny Meemaw 90th birthday celebration. Talk about the start of a memorable summer.
        If Greg can finagle his way into a Mac Digby video, not only will it eclipse all this Diaper Hand business, why, it will redeem the whole summer. … No, it will make his whole life.
    </string>
</resources>
